# KOMSUN KOMOLJINDAKUL

Software Engineer - Backend (Ruby on Rails)

#### **OVERVIEW**

I have been working on web development for more than ten years through many projects for a variety of companies. I worked on both backend and full-stack development.

My primary development stack is Ruby on Rails, Vue.js, and PostgreSQL. If necessary, I am also open to leveraging new programming languages, e.g., Go, Elixir, and Rust.

# **SKILLS**

Web Development with Ruby on Rails/ PostgreSQL/ MongoDB/ Redis Vue.js/ JavaScript ES6 CSS frameworks: Bulma, Bootstrap

# **EDUCATION**

Master degree in Information Technology
King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **DATA WOW**

Senior Software Engineer - Backend Sep 2021 - Present

- Developed web applications for client projects
- Improved and created new features for in-house web applications
- Solved 75% of critical bugs on an end-to-end computer vision platform

#### **BLUEPATTERN**

Senior Software Engineer Dec 2018 - Aug 2021

- Developed a social application on the stack of Ruby on Rails and Vue.js
- Developed mobile iOS/Android application
- Created the prototype and made UX/UI designs

#### **OMISE**

Senior Ruby on Rails Developer Jan 2020 - Nov 2020

- Built the logic for the payment gateway platform based on credit card networks
- Created and improved the service API

#### **SENNALABS**

Senior Ruby on Rails Developer/ Team Lead

Feb 2018 - Nov 2018

- Developed web applications for client projects
- Improved and created new features for the company startup project
- Reduced SMS costs by 95% by offering and implementing another service provider

#### **LOCKSTEP LABS**

Full-stack Ruby on Rails Developer Oct 2017 - Jan 2018

- Developed web applications for client projects

#### **HIPFLAT**

Full-stack Ruby on Rails Developer Aug 2015 - Sep 2017

- Improved and created new features for the online real estate search portal (company startup project)
- Validated and prepared incoming data

## TURK ENTERPRISES INC.

Back-End Developer (PHP)
Jul 2012 - Mar 2014

- Developed e-commerce modules that are specific to the funeral business
- Integrated payment gateways, e.g., WonderPay, Authorize, and Bluefin into applications

## **EXASITES**

Full-stack Web Developer / Team Lead (PHP)
Mar 2009 - Oct 2010

- Created, developed, and customized web applications based on the company framework
- Coordinated with the SEO team to make websites with high rankings on search portals

## **MY CONTACT**

Email: komoljindakul@hotmail.com

Location: Bangkok, Thailand